莉莉丝 我杀了她 并且释放了路西法
Lilith, what's the funny see. I killed her, and I set Lucifer free.
你背弃了兄弟 选择了恶魔
You chose a demon over your own brother.
我已经无法再信任你了
I just don't think I can trust you.
你觉得我仍会禁不住诱惑
You think I'll take one look at a demon.
看到恶魔就会想扑上去吸血
And suddenly fall off the wagon,
我已经吃一堑了 难道还不会长一智
As if, after everything, I haven't learned my lesson.
噢 真长了吗
Well, have you?
- 我知道你不再信任我了 - 什么意思
- I know you don't trust me. - So, what are you saying?
也许分开行动对咱俩会更好
Maybe it's best we just go our separate ways.
我也这么想
Well, I think you're right.
- 你知道我是谁 - 路西法
- You know who I am. - Lucifer.
非你莫属 萨姆 专属于我的皮囊
You're the one, Sam. you're my vessel.
想都别想
That'll never happen.
你是米迦勒之剑
You're the michael sword.
- 我是剑 什么意思 - 你是米迦勒的利器
- What do you mean, I'm the sword? - You're michael's weapon.
- 意思就是我是皮囊吗 - 你是独一无二的皮囊
- I'm a vessel? - You're the vessel.
想回来吗
You want back in…
- 我绝不会让你失望的 - 我知道
- I won't let you down. - Oh, I know it.
（如今）
行了 伙计 到底有什么重要的事儿
All right, buddy, what's so important.
不能在手机上说啊
You couldn't tell me over the phone?
相信我 吉姆
Trust me, Jim.
这绝对万分重要
It's important.
等等 你不会是
Wait a minute. you're not …
别跟我说这就是
You're not telling me that this is…
- 没错 - 你找到了
- Yep. - You found it.
小贱货
Little Bastard.
噢 你找到了
Ohh, you found it.
偶 滴 神 啊
Oh…my…god.
是真货
Are you sure?
还是比赛时的车牌号
Vin number's a match.
花了多少银子啊
How much did you pay?
一大笔
A lot.
得了 快说是多少
Come on. how much?
很大一笔
A lot.
那是肯定的
I'll bet.
你还没发动过吗
You start her up yet?
就等着你啊
Been waiting for you.
嗯 是想在我面前好好炫耀一番吧
Yeah, waiting to rub my nose in it, right?
真了解我
Exactly.
等等 先等一下
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
这种历史性的时刻一定得录下来才行
We need to record this for posterity's sake.
好主意
Great idea.
当然是个好主意
Yeah. great idea.
真是
That…
评论家称其为诱骗
The critics call it a blockbust…
卡尔
Cal?!
卡尔 嘿 你没事吧
Cal?! Hey, you all right, man?
貌似我听到什么声音了
I thought I heard something.
卡尔 出什么事儿了吗
Cal, there's something wrong?
偶滴神啊
Oh, my god.
卡尔
Cal!
对了 这次是什么活儿来着
So, what's with this job?
有钱公子哥儿竟把头猛撞向停得纹丝不动的汽车上
Dude suffers a head-on collision in a parked car?
这绝对值得我们一探究竟
I'd say that's worth checking out.
当然 当然
Yeah, definitely.
但我们还有更重要的问题要解决 不是吗
Uh, but we got bigger problems, don't you think?
我想天启绝不会自己长脚跑掉的
I'm sure the apocalypse will still be there when we get back.
对 话是没错 但是
Right, yeah, but, I mean,
如果科尔特枪真的流落在外的话
If the Colt is really out there somewhere …
是啊 我们已经找了整整三个星期了 还是一无所获
Yeah, we've been looking for three weeks. we got bupkus.
我知道
Okay.
但是 迪恩
But, Dean…
如果我们想干掉恶魔
I mean, if we're gonna ice the devil …
我们这不就正在干吗
This is what we're doing, okay?
争论到此结束
End of discussion.
这可是我们再在一起之后的
It's just that this is our first real case.
第一件真真切切的案子
Back at it together.
我觉得我们都该放松点儿
You know, I think we ought to ease into it,
借此重新找回默契
Put the training wheels back on.
所以你觉得我需要重新训练下了
So you think I need training wheels?
不 是我们 我们都需要重新训练下
No."we." we need training wheels.
你和我 作为一体
You and me, as a team.
明白了吗
Okay?
明白
Okay.
我真的希望这是一次新的开始 了解吗
I mean, I really want this to be a fresh start, you know?
是对我们俩而言
For the both of us.
了解
Okay.
（坎顿 俄亥俄州）
探员博纳姆和科普兰
Agents Bonham and Copeland.
瑞克·卡内基 很高兴见到你们
Rick Carnegie. Good to know you.
- 你们是来调查卡尔·霍普金斯的死亡原因的 - 没错
- So you're here on account of Cal Hopkins' death? - That's right.
那恐怕真是有的查了啊
Well, afraid you came a long way for nothing.
我们已经抓到凶手了
We already booked the guy that did it.
不好意思 你说是谁干的
I'm sorry. who do you think did it?
卡尔 怎么了 天啊 卡尔
Cal, something wrong? God…Cal!
那个变态拍下了自己的杰作
Sicko taped his own handiwork.
我不太明白你的意思
I don't follow.
是吉姆·格罗斯曼杀了卡尔
It was Jim Grossman that killed cal.
等等 你说什么
Wait. what?
他是方圆百里内唯一在现场的人
Well, he was the only one on the scene for miles.
他们是最好的朋友
They were best friends.
大多数暴力犯罪
Most violent crimes are committed.
都发生在密友之间
By someone close to the victim.
卡尔是被时速80英里的冲击撞到挡风玻璃上
And how exactly did Jim slam Cal into a windshield.
吉姆到底是怎么做到的呢
With all the force of an 80-mile-per-hour crash?
大概是嗑了药
Drugs, maybe?
听着 要知道这又不是脑手术 伙计们
Look, you know this ain't brain surgery, boys.
真相通常就是表面看上去的那样
Whatever it looks like, that's what it usually is.
简单明了
It's simple.
「简单明了」 好吧
"simple." right.
那好吧
Right.
如果你不介意
Um, if you don't mind,
我们还是想和吉姆·格罗斯曼谈谈
We'd like to speak to Jim Grossman anyway.
当时我正在屋子里
I was in the house when it happened.
我甚至什么都没看到
I didn't even see it.
为方便起见 我们其实是相信你的
And for argument's sake, say we believe you.
为什么 警察可不信我
Why would you? the cops didn't.
我们不是普通的警察
We're not your typical cops.
请告诉我们你看见了什么
Please, just tell us what you saw.
我没看见 而是听见有动静
It's not what I saw. it's what I heard.
轮胎刺耳的摩擦和玻璃打碎的声音
Tires squealing, glass breaking.
是那辆车干的
It was the car that did it.
车
The car?
我是指 我听说过有关诅咒的传闻
I mean, I heard about the curse,
但我一直不以为然
But I just thought it was a load of crap.
诅咒 什么诅咒
Curse? what do you mean, curse?
那辆车的诅咒 小贱货
The car. little bastard.
小 小贱货
L-little bastard?
他是在车里被杀的吗
As in the little bastard?
等等 什么是「小贱货」
Wait, wait. what's little bastard?
是詹姆士·迪恩的车 他就在车里被杀
It's James Dean's car. it's the one he was killed in.
是的 就是她
Yeah, that's the one.
卡尔已经找寻了多年
Cal had been looking for it for years.
其实 见鬼的 我们都找了很多年
I mean, hell, we both had.
但是他先找到了
But he found it first.
我们必须得查清楚这事
Oh, we are definitely checking this out.
这个就像是「妖车克里斯汀」的故事吗
So what this is like the "Christine"?
不 「妖车克里斯汀」只是小说
No, "Christine" is fiction.
而这
This …
这可是千真万确的事实
This is real.
好吧 那就说来听听
Okay. enlighten me.
詹姆士·迪恩去世后
Well, after James Dean died,
他的机械师买下了汽车残骸
His mechanic bought the wreckage,
重新修理好了
And he fixed it up.
但结果就是他被这辆车压死了
And it repaid him by falling on him.
然后是托尼·麦凯亨利被杀
Then Tony Mchenry was killed.
这辆车在赛道上自动上锁
When it locked up on the racetrack.
我是指 死亡如同尾气一般缠绕着这辆车
I mean, death follows this car around like exhaust.
所有人都对她敬而远之
Nobody touches it and comes away in one piece.
直到1970年 她从卡车的车厢内消失了
Then in 1970, it vanished off the back of a truck.
自从那时起 就再也没人见过她
Nobody's ever seen it since.
我告诉你 老弟 如果
I'm telling you, man. if this …
如果这辆车就是那辆小贱货
If this car is little bastard,
一定就是她杀了那个人
I will bet you dollars to doughnuts.
让我赌啥都成
It's what killed the guy.
好吧 那我们怎么查
So, how do we find out?
卡尔曾说汽车识别代码是吻合的
Well, Cal matched the vin number,
但只有通过引擎代码才能知道
But the only real way to know is the engine number.
我想引擎代码应该
I'm guessing the engine number …
是在引擎上的 没错
On the engine. yeah.
要我来吗
You want me to do it?
不用
No.
不不 我能搞定
No, no, i've g… i've got it.
好吧 宝贝儿
Okay, baby…
我不会伤害你的 所以
I'm not gonna hurt you, so…
你也别害我
Don't hurt me.
要手电筒吗
Need a flashlight?
不要
No.
啥都别做 快走开
Don't do anything. just go away.
你 呃 好吧
You … uh, okay.
别出声 行吗
Don't speak, all right?
也别盯着她看 她可能会不喜欢
In fact, don't even look at her. she might not like it.
查出之前的车主来
Find out who owned it.
不止是上一任车主
Not just the last owner…
你得一直追查到1955年
You got to take it all the way back to 1955.
这样调查工作量很大
That's a lot of research.
看来你今天下午有事做了
Well, I guess I just made your afternoon.
那么说你想当演员
So, you want to be an actress, huh?
这可巧了
That is …that is so funny.
因为我正是
Because I am actually…
威廉·莫里斯公司的经纪人
An agent for William Morris Endeavor.
再帮我满上好吗
You mind filling me up again?
你就是明星 知道吗
Hey, you're a star, all right?
花了些工夫
Hey, took me a while,
但是我追查了所有的前车主
But I traced all the car's previous owners.
他们中有没有人是横死的
Any of them die bloody?
没有 实际上
Nope. In fact…
迪恩 你在酒吧吗
Dean, are you in a bar?
不是 我在 我在餐馆
No, I'm …I'm in a restaurant…
你的啤酒
Here's your beer.
谢谢
Thanks.
这家餐馆碰巧有吧台
…that happens to have a bar.
我在这边忙得要死
I've been working my ass off here.
同病相怜 兄弟
Hey, world's smallest violin, pal.
我查克里斯汀查了一下午
I spent the afternoon up Christine's skirt.
我需要喝一杯
I needed a drink.
其实用不着
Actually, you didn't.
什么意思
Meaning?
第一个车主是费城的一位心脏病专家
The car's first owner was a cardiologist.
直到1972年去世他一直开着这部车
In philadelphia …drove it till he died in 1972.
你的意思是
So you're saying…
这辆保时捷从来就不是
That porsche is not, nor has it ever been,
詹姆斯·迪恩的车
James Dean's car.
这辆「小贱货」是假的
It's a fake little bastard.
好吧 那么人是什么杀的
Well, then, what was it that killed the guy?
问得好
Good question.
好了 希尔先生 我完事了
Okay, Mr. Hill. I finish.
谢谢你 康斯薇拉 祝你今晚过得愉快
Thank you, Consuela. Have a good night.
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
是你
It's you.
可是你已经死了
But you're dead.
你应该已经死了
You're supposed to be dead.
不要
No.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
你们要仔细搜索
I want you to use a fine-tooth comb.
证据就在这里 我们只需要找到它
The evidence is here. Just got to find it.
听说你又遇上奇案了
Heard you got another weird one.
表 表面上看
Well, it's a …it's a little.
是有点儿奇怪
Strange on the surface…
但只要看看证据
But, you know, once y-you look at the facts…
威廉·希尔死于头部中弹
William Hill died from a gunshot wound to the head.
没有枪支 没有火药 没有子弹
No gun, no gunpowder, no bullet.
没有 但也没什么奇怪的
Nope. Nothin' strange about that.
总该有个合乎逻辑的解释
Well, there's got to be a reasonable explanation.
一定有的
There always is.
那你合乎逻辑的解释是
Well, what's your reasonable explanation?
职业杀手
Professional killer.
再说一遍
Come again?
中情局 国家安全局 他们有一伙特训刺客
CIA, NSA, one of them trained assassins…
就像《迈克尔·克莱顿》里演的那样
Like in "Michael Clayton".
太对了
Right.
你们可以随意看看
You're welcome to look around, but…
但是这些人不留指纹
But these guys don't leave fingerprints.
你不介意我们跟目击证人谈谈吧
Mind if we talk with the witness?
随意 她讲的话毫无道理
Oh, be my guest. She's not making any sense.
你就是懂西班牙语也听不明白
And she's not making any sense in Spanish, either.
正是
Right.
[西班牙语] 我不能住在这 我有自己的家庭
No puedo vivir aqu? Necesito mI familia.
我现在要回去 我要回家
Me voy ahora. Me voy a la casa.
不是 我家在萨尔瓦多
No… Me voy a la casa en el salvador ahora.
康斯薇拉·阿尔瓦雷茨
Consuela Alvarez?
是我
Yes?
联调局
FBI.
你说你看到有什么东西
Now, you said you saw something.
在教授房子里
In the professor's house.
是吗 从窗户里看见的
Right? Something in the window.
我当时正在倒垃圾桶
Estaba sacando la basura.
[西班牙语] 然后？
Y luego.
[西班牙语] 女士 不要怕 慢慢说
No tengas miedo de hablar despacio.
[西班牙语] 那个人什么样子
Como era ese hombre?
不错啊
Nice.
大学一年级学的西班牙语
Freshman Spanish.
他很高 非常高
Era alto, muy alto.
穿着黑色长外套
Y llevaba el abrigo negro largo.
懂了
Okay, uh…
一个男人 非常高
Tall man. Very tall.
穿了一件长黑袍
With a long black coat.
有大胡子对吧 有胡子
And, uh, a beard? beard.
有一顶帽子
Y un sombrero.
一个戴墨西哥帽的男人吗？
Dude was wearing a sombrero?
就是一顶帽子
A-a hat. not a-a …
不是的 是很高的那种帽子
No, no, no. un sombrero alto.
- 高顶帽吗 - 应该是顶帽
- A tall hat? oh, - Like a top hat?
是那种高帽
Iun sombrero alto!
很高的那种
Muy alto.
你是说
What, you mean like a …
- 有点像大礼帽吗 - 没错
- Like a stovepipe hat? - Si?
我知道了 和亚伯拉罕·林肯很像
Oh, yeah, you know, like abraham lincoln.
是 就是林肯总统
Si? el presidente lincoln.
亚伯拉罕·林肯杀了希尔先生
Abraham lincoln killed mr. hill.
我现在能回家了吗
S-so I go home now?
当然 十分感谢
Uh, si? gracias.
谢谢
Gracias.
怎么了
What?
这是金·罗斯曼视频里的定格画面
Here's a freeze-frame from jim grossman's video.
是我疯了还是里面那人真得很像詹姆斯·迪恩
Am I crazy, or does that look like james dean?
看上去挺像詹姆斯·迪恩
That looks like james dean.
现在疑犯有亚伯拉罕·林肯和詹姆斯·迪恩
So, we got abraham lincoln and james dean?
都是名人鬼
Famous ghosts?
也许吧
Maybe.
太疯狂了
Well, that's just silly.
不是 实际上 名人鬼魂数不胜数
No, actually, uh, there's a ton of lore on famous ghosts.
甚至比平民鬼魂多
More than the, you know, not-famous kinds.
我倒是很好奇之前一次都没碰到过
I'm actually surprised we haven't run into one before.
是呀 现在就来了2个
Yeah, but now we got two of them?
2个极度愤怒的鬼魂
two extremely pissed off ghosts?
- 显然是鬼魂在和粉丝套近乎 - 此话怎讲
- Who are apparently ganking their fans. - What do you mean?
希尔教授对于美国内战深有造诣
Professor hill was a civil war nut.
他是林肯的拥护者
He dug lincoln.
那卡尔一定是詹姆斯·迪恩的拥趸
And cal must have been a james dean freak.
他花了整整17年的时间来寻找偶像拥有的车
He spent 17 years of his life tracking down the guy's car.
你是说这次我们遇到的是
So, you're saying that we've got.
2个超级有名 超级愤怒的鬼魂
Two super-famous, super-pissed-off ghosts.
杀害自己的超级粉丝咯
Killing their super fans?
看上去是这样的
That's what it looks like.
这也太异想天开了
Well, that is muchos loco.
应该用「muy」
"muy".
而不是「muchos」
Not "muchos".
好吧 至关重要的是
Yeah, well, the big question is,
我们下一步该怎么走
What the hell are they doing here?
没错 鬼魂通常在生前的故居周围出现
Yeah, ghosts usually haunt the places they lived.
就是说 亚伯拉罕·林肯住在白宫
I mean, I get abraham lincoln at the white house.
詹姆斯·迪恩待在赛车场 但是…
And james dean at a racetrack, but…
那他们到坎顿来做什么
What the hell are they doing in canton?
搞什么飞机
You got to be kidding me.
怎么了
What?
搞什么飞机
You got to be kidding me.
老弟 他好矮
Dude he is short.
甘地可是位伟人
Gandhi was a great man.
好像蓝精灵
Yeah, for a smurf.
抱歉让你们久等了
Oh, sorry to keep you waiting.
现在是我们一年里最忙的时候
This is our busiest time of the year.
这还算忙
This is busy?
不是现在 还早着呢
W-well, n-not right now. but it's early.
都4点半了
4:30.
有什么能为您效劳的
So, what can I do for you?
我们在撰写一份旅行杂志
Well, we are writing a piece for travel magazine.
没错 寻找最货真价实的蜡像馆
Yeah, on how totally non-sucky wax museums are.
太棒了
That's fantastic!
一些媒体的宣传 这正是我们需要的
A little press … just what we need.
那太好了 我们对你们馆一些展品比较感兴趣
Great, well, we're interested in a few of your exhibits,
尤其是亚伯拉罕·林肯和詹姆斯·迪恩那两尊
Specifically abraham lincoln and james dean.
这是我们馆最受欢迎的展品
Two of our most popular displays.
是吗 这么说吸引了很多游客咯
Oh, yeah? so they bring in a lot of visitors?
没错 有很多常客
Yeah, we have our regulars.
该不会恰巧
I don't suppose.
威廉·希尔和卡尔·霍普金斯
That william hill and cal hopkins.
就是你们的常客吧
Were regulars, were they?
事实上 是的
As a matter of fact, they were.
我听说了他们的事 太悲惨了
I heard what happened to them. that's tragic, just tragic.
这个不会写到文章里去吧 是吧
Well, that's not gonna be in the article, is it?
当然不会
No. no, no. of course not.
我不得不说
You know, I got to tell you,
那尊林肯的蜡像 太逼真了
That … that lincoln is so lifelike.
他是如此的栩栩如生 简直像能活动一样
I mean, you know, you can just imagine him moving around.
你见过那样的没
You ever see anything like that?
呃 没
Uh, no.
你觉得 有没有什么东西
Well, is there anything you can think of.
会令你的博物馆不同寻常
That would make your museum…unusual?
是为了写文章
You know, for the article.
我敢说 这世上绝对没有
Well, i'll say. there isn't another.
第二个像我这里的地方
place like us,
- 为什么 - 这帽子是林肯的真品
- How so? - Well, for one, that's honest abe's real hat.
真的吗
It is?
也就是他的遗物
Almost like his remains.
算是吧
Ugh. I guess.
你不会恰好有
You wouldn't happen to have.
詹姆斯·迪恩的遗物吧
Any of james dean's personal effects, would you?
恩 有个他的钥匙链
Yeah, got his key chain.
我们有好多这样的东西
We got a bunch of stuff …
甘地的双光眼镜 罗斯福的人工呼吸器
Uh, gandhi's bifocals, fdr's iron lung,
这个
This.
这是谁的呢
And who did that belong to?
方兹（美国著名科幻演员）从第二季到第四季
The fonzie seasons 2 through 4.
这倒是挺酷的
Yeah, that's … that's really cool…ish.
这算什么
Oh, this? this is nothing.
我一直在收集一些东西
I've been working on a new collection of figures,
能够让孩子们惊呼的那种
Stuff that'll really wow the kids.
- 孩子 - “Y世代”的东西
- The kids? - Yeah, Gen "Y".
电脑游戏 手机 等等
Computer games, cellphones, "sexting" …
联邦特工的那些东西
They're just fads.
我会让蜡像馆再度风靡
I'm gonna make wax museums hip again.
亚伯拉罕·林肯和詹姆斯·迪恩
Yeah, abraham lincoln and james dean.
真是难以置信
Can you believe that?
为啥那么疯狂的想杀人
Why so kill-crazy?
也许天启导致这一切吧
Ah, maybe the apocalypse has got them all hot and bothered.
恩 大家都知道这是谁的错
Yeah, well, we all know whose fault that is.
恩 我会留意他的
Yeah, i'm keeping an eye on him.
回头打给你 再见
I'll call you later. bye.
怎么了
What's going on?
你打包好了吗
Did you get the trunk packed up?
恩 都扔后备箱了 你跟谁在打电话
Yeah, the trunk's packed. who was on the phone?
- 鲍比 - 然后呢
- Bobby. - And?
没什么
Nothing.
那我就假装没听到
So, we're just gonna pretend i.
刚才我所听到的吗
didn't hear what I just heard.
爱装不装 随你便
Pretend or don't pretend, whatever floats your boat.
这不应该是个崭新的开始吗
This was supposed to be a fresh start, dean.
对啊 这不就是崭新了吗
Well, this is about as fresh as it gets.
到底走不走
Now, we going or not?
看着
Check it out.
87年前
Four score and seven years ago,
我有个搞笑的帽子
I had a funny hat.
迪恩
Dean.
我不能玩玩这个么
I can't have any fun with this?
把东西烧了 连鬼魂也一起烧掉吧
Let's just torch the objects, torch the ghosts,
然后闪人 好不好
And get out of here, okay?
我去拿「伊甸园之东」的钥匙扣
I'll go grab "east of eden's" key chain.
迪恩
Dean!
- 是甘地吗 - 是
- Is that gandhi?! - Yeah!
哥们 他真是个疯子
Dude, he's squirrelly.
拿那个
Get the …
拿什么
Get the what?!
眼镜
Glasses!
你就不能崇拜些比较酷的人么
You couldn't have been a fan of someone cool?
真的假的 甘地
Really? gandhi?
准备闪人没有
You ready to blow this joint?
迪恩 你不觉得有些奇怪吗
Dean, didn't it strike you as strange,
甘地消失的方式
The way gandhi just vanished?
怎么奇怪
Strange how?
没尖叫 没火烧
No screaming, no big flameout.
这可不是通常鬼魂消失的方式
I mean, that isn't the way ghosts usually go.
我烧 他消失 搞定
Still … I torched, he vanished.
话没错 但是
Yeah, but I …
但是我觉得他
Also, I feel like he was…
他想要咬我一口
Took e a bite out of me.
咬你
A bite?
恩 就好像他很饿一样
Yeah, like he was hungry.
但是问题是 真的甘地
But the thing is, gandhi … or the real gandhi …
他是
He was a …
什么
A what?
说啊
Spit it out.
他是果食主义者
He was a fruitarian.
让我来理一下思绪
Let me get this straight.
你崇拜的英雄
Your ultimate hero.
不仅仅是一个穿着麻布衣的矮子
Was not only a short man in diapers,
还是个果食主义者
But he was also a fruitarian?
- 这不是重点 - 这没错
- That's not the point. - That is good.
对你来说 这已经很不错了
That is … even for you, that is good.
我只是觉得这事不会轻易结束
Look, i'm just saying i'm not so sure this thing is over.
它只是个幽灵
It was a ghost.
还是个超级古怪的果食主义幽灵
It was a weirdly supercharged fruitarian ghost.
说到底还是个幽灵 好吧 我们走
But it was still a ghost. now let's go.
好吧 首先你强拉我进小镇
So, first, you drag me into town,
现在又活生生的把我拖出来
And now you're dragging me back out?
因为你是死脑筋
You ain't steering this boat.
快点走吧
Let's go. chop-chop.
这可不适合一起干下去
You know, this isn't gonna work.
你说什么
What isn't?
我们 你和我
Us. you, me … together.
我以为可以 但这不行
I thought it could, but it can't.
可是你想回来的哦 长官
You're the one that wanted back in, chief.
不过让我回来的可是你
And you're the one who called me back in.
我仍觉得我们该做一些建立信任的事情
I still think we got some trust-building to do.
那还要多久才能换回你的信任
How long am I gonna be on double-secret probation?
我说了算
Until I say so.
我知道我过去的所作所为
Look… I know what I did, What i've done.
我正在努力爬出这个深渊
And I am trying to climb out of that hole.
我坚信
I am.
但你让这变得困难重重
But you're not making it any easier.
你希望我忘掉你过去的一切
So, what, am I supposed to just let you off the hook?
不 你想怎么样都可以
No. you can think whatever you want.
我应当接受惩罚
I deserve it and worse.
你对我的惩罚还没我对我自己的多
Hell, you'll never punish me as much as i'm punish myself.
但问题是
But the point is,
如果我和你是一体
If we're gonna be a team, you and i,
那肯定是条双行道
It has to be a two-way street.
我们得回到过去的老路
So we just go back to the way we were before?
不 因为我们之前没有走过那路
No, because we were never that way before.
没有干活之前
"before" didn't work.
我们在这儿是为了什么
How do you think we got here?
那应该是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
迪恩 当时和露比走的唯一理由是
Dean, one of the reasons I went off with ruby…
是远离你
Was to get away from you.
什么
What?
让我变得很强
It made me feel strong,
变得不像是你的弟弟
Like I wasn't your kid brother.
你有说过这是我的错么
Are you saying this is my fault?
没有 错的是我
No, it's my fault.
如果我们干下去
All i'm saying is that if we're gonna do this,
就得与众不同
We have to do it different.
我们不能两次跨入同一条河流
We can't just fall into the same rut.
你要我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
让我崛起 从头开始
You're gonna have to let me grow up, for starters.
是我 好的 马上到
Yeah. yeah, okay.
我想这次你对了 这事儿没完
I guess you were right about this not being over.
卡内基警长
Sheriff carnegie.
什么事 警长
Sheriff, what happened?
我
I, uh, um…
我不知道怎么说
I don't know.
打扰下 姑娘们 我们是联邦探员
Excuse us, girls. hi, we're with the fbi.
能否告诉我们发生了什么
Can you tell us what happened?
这太恐怖了
It was horrible.
恐怖的不行
Way horrible.
什么恐怖
What was horrible?
我觉得她是个好人
I thought she'd be nice.
我现在还不能相信
I still can't believe it.
相信什么
Believe what?
她杀死了丹妮尔
She took danielle!
谁干的
Who?
别怕 这很安全 把事情告诉我们
It's okay. you're safe. just tell us.
谁杀死了你们的朋友
Who took your friend?
是
It was…
帕丽斯·希尔顿
Paris hilton.
什么
Sorry?
虽然她看起来真的很棒
She looked really good, though.
很苗条很放荡
Skinny. skinny and fast.
他们去哪儿了
Um, where did they go?
不知道
We don't know.
消失了
They just vanished.
不介意我们离开一会儿么
Would you excuse us for just a minute?
帕丽斯·希尔顿还没死吧
Paris hilton's not dead, as far as we know, right?
我确信 没死
Pretty sure, no.
这就意味着不是
Which means it's not a…
- 鬼怪作怪 - 的确不是
- Ghost. - No.
所以要么帕丽斯·希尔顿是杀人狂
So either Paris Hilton is a homicidal maniac or …
要么我们遗漏了某些细节
Or we missed something.
你有什么打算
What do you want to do?
真是恶心
Whew! that's ripe.
这是什么鬼玩意
What the hell?
真不敢相信我竟然遗漏了
I can't believe I missed it.
遗漏了什么
Missed what?
仔细回顾下另两个受害人
Went back over the other two vics.
他们都大量失血
There was blood loss … major.
正常啊 你要是被残忍杀害也会这样
Yeah, well, being a gory smear will do that to you.
不不 我是说失血量
No, no, I mean more blood loss.
远比车祸或是爆头要多得多
Than a car crash or a head wound should cause.
更像是 被人吸食了
Almost like… something's feeding.
是啊 真恐怖
Yeah. awesome.
对了 还发现了这个
And then… there were these.
这是什么 种子吗
What are those, seeds?
是的 在受害人的肚子里
Yeah, they were in both vics' bellies.
你洗手了吧
I hope you washed your hands.
这跟我之前见过的种子不一样 迪恩
They're unlike any other seed i've ever seen before, dean.
我以为你不会那么无趣
Wow, just when I thought you couldn't get any geekier.
有了
Yahtzee!
什么玩意
What?
这一带不产这种种子
The seeds aren't from around here.
实际上 我国境内的树和植物也不结
In fact, they're not from any tree or plant in the country.
那是哪里产的
Where are they from?
东欧 巴尔干地区的密林里
Eastern europe, from a forest in the balkans,
事实上那儿也不产了
Which is not even there anymore.
30年前这些树被砍了
It was chopped down like 30 years ago.
然后呢
So?
当地有个传说 那片密林由一个
So, local legend has it that the forest was guarded.
名字叫莱希的异教神所守护
By a pagan god whose name was leshii …
他是一个淘气的小神 可以千变万化
A mischievous god, could take on infinite forms.
让我猜猜 他爱吃自己的粉丝
And let me guess … he liked to munch on his fans.
只能通过吸食教徒之血
"could be appeased only with the.
才得以满足
blood from his worhippers.
他将他们吸干
It would drain them.
然后将种子放进他们胃里
Then stuff their stomachs with the seeds.
他怎么办到的
How's he doing it?
通过触碰詹姆斯·迪恩的钥匙链
What, he touches james dean's key chain.
就能摇身变为詹姆斯·迪恩了吗
And then morphs into james dean?
有这种可能
Hmm. that's good a guess as any.
好吧 随便吧 关键是我们怎么才能杀掉他
Yeah, well, whatever. how do we kill him?
这上面说用纯铁斧砍掉他的脑袋
Says here to chop off his head with an iron ax.
好吧
All right.
我们去抓那个帕丽斯·希尔顿吧
Let's go gank ourselves a paris hilton.
她还活着吗
She alive?
活着 但气若悬丝了
Yeah, barely.
太棒了
Awesome.
真高兴你们及时醒过来了
I'm so glad you're awake for this.
接下来的会更精彩
This is gonna be huge.
好极了 看来我不会错过了
Super. I wouldn't want to miss it.
我是说 我刚刚吃完
I mean, i've been stuffing myself with fast food lately.
顺便做个宗教仪式
So it's nice to do the ritual right,
或许细细品尝 换换口味也不错
Prepare a nice, slow meal for a change.
就像过去一样吗
Just like the good old days, huh?
你根本不了解
You have no idea.
人们崇敬我
People adored me.
他们过去常常微笑着
They used to throw themselves at me,
献身于我
With smiles on their faces.
是啊 我猜这些年 没人对这些
Yeah, I guess these days, nobody gives a flying crap.
荒郊野林的神感兴趣了吧
About some backwoods-forest god, huh?
不对 还不是因为他们砍了我的密林
No, not since they cut down my forest.
建了个南斯拉夫工厂
To build a yugo plant.
时代在进步 小妹
March of progress, sister.
这么多年来 我到处闲逛
For years now, i've been wandering.
饥饿 恐惧
Hungry. scared.
四处寻找残羹剩饭
Scrounging for scraps.
有点惹人厌
So not sexy.
但之后
But then…
神奇的事情发生了
The best thing ever happened …
有人开启了天启
Someone tripped the apocalypse.
我就想 搞什么
And I thought, what the hell …
我受够了以往的事物
I'm tired of watching what I eat.
我要吃大餐
I want to pig out.
所以就找到了这个小地方
So I found this little place.
这儿太棒了
It's awesome.
虔诚的粉丝蜂拥而至
Adoring fans stroll right in the door.
是啊 但他们不是你的粉丝
Yeah. but they're not your fans.
那又怎样
So?
他们崇拜的是林肯 甘地 希尔顿
They worship lincoln, gandhi, hilton.
不管怎样 我会拿走我能得到的一切
Whatever. i'll take what I can get.
你知道 我告诉过你
You know, I got to tell you,
你不是我们遇到的第一位神
You are not the first god we've met,
但你却是最狂热的
But you are the nuttiest.
不 是你们 你们人类
No. you. you people.
你们才是疯狂的那类
You're the crazy ones.
你们曾经尊崇神灵
You used to worship gods.
但此时
But this?
这被误认为什么偶像崇拜
This is what passes for idolatry?
社会名流
Celebrities?
他们除了小狗和美容还有什么
What have they got besides small dogs and spray tans?
你们人类过去一直怀有旧式的宗教信仰
You people used to have old-time religion.
现在则是每周一次
Now you have us weekly.
我不知道
I don't know.
我在“阁楼”（美国色情杂志论坛）论坛发了不少帖子
I'm more of a penthouse forum man, myself.
也许是吧 但是
Maybe, but…
这里仍有许多美味的肉在那些骨头上 帅哥
There's still a lot of yummy meat on those bones, boy.
好吧 我本不愿意向你透露实情的 美女 但是
Well, I hate to break it to you, sister, but, uh…
你不能吃我
You can't eat me.
听着 我不是一个帕丽斯·希尔顿永远的最好的朋友
See, i'm not a paris hilton bff.
我也从未看过“恐怖蜡像馆”
I've never even seen "house of wax."
不
No.
但我可以完全看穿你的想法 迪恩
But I can totally read your mind, dean.
我知道谁才是你的英雄
I know who your hero is.
你的父亲
Your daddy.
我说对了吗
Am I right?
这个曾属于他
And this belonged to him.
不是吗
Didn't it?
可怜的小迪恩
Poor little dean.
所有你曾经想要的就是被你的偶像所爱
All you ever wanted was to be loved by your idol.
一个遥远的父亲形象正在升起
One distant father figure, coming right up!
什么也别说
Not a word.
兄弟
Dude.
你刚和帕丽斯·希尔顿过了一小段美好时光
You just got whaled on by paris hilton.
闭嘴
Shut up.
好吧 谢谢
All right. thank you.
卡内基警长
Sheriff carnegie.
丹妮尔会没事的
Danielle's gonna be all right.
她已经离开“简单生活”
She's sworn off "the simple life, "
但除此之外
But other than that…
很高兴她没事
Glad she's okay.
会转好的
It gets better …
警长已经发出对帕丽斯·希尔顿的全境通告
Sheriff's putting out an apb on paris hilton.
那应该有作用
That ought to be good.
听着 我在想你昨天说的
Hey, listen, I was thinking about what you said yesterday …
关于我看你太紧了的问题
About me keeping too tight of a leash on you.
也许你是对的
Well, maybe you're right.
我的意思是 看 我也不并不是清白先生
I mean, look, i'm not exactly mr. innocent.
在这整件事上
In this whole mess, either.
你知道 是我打破了第一个封印
You know, I did break the first seal.
- 你当时并不知情 - 是的 你不也是
- You didn't know. - Yeah, well, neither did you.
我不是说恶魔血液是一个可行的好方法
I'm not saying demon blood was a great way to go,
但是你杀死了莉莉丝
But you did kill lilith.
- 然而打开了天启 - 我们不也看到了未来么
- And start the apocalypse. - Which neither of us saw coming.
我的意思是 谁会想到杀死莉莉丝会有不好的一天
I mean, who would've thought killing lilith would've bad day.
重点是 我很担心监视你的一举一动
Point is, I was so worried about watching your every move.
我没有看到你实际做的原因
That I didn't see what it was actually doing to you.
所以对此 我很抱歉
So, for that, i'm sorry.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们从这里去哪里
So, where do we go from here?
我已经看到了我们的生存之道
The way I see it, we got one shot at surviving this.
那是什么
What's that?
大概我为恶魔准备齐全了
Maybe I am on deck for the devil.
大概你和米伽勒也一样
Maybe the same with you and michael.
也许没有改变
Maybe there's no changing that.
那还是很鼓舞人心的
Well, that's encouraging.
但我们不能撒手不管
But we can stop wringing our hands over it.
我们抢先抓住任何在我们前面的东西
We got to just grab on to whatever's in front of us,
干掉它 打败它
Kick its ass, and go down fighting.
我可以继续搭伙
I can get on board with that.
好的
Okay.
但我们要在同一水平上做
But we're gonna have to do it on the same level.
你懂的
You got it.
你说我们要离开这里
What do you say we get the hell out of here?
你想开车吗
You want to drive?
你确定
You sure?
是的 我得打个小盹
Yeah. I could, uh … I could use a nap.